thank you
[Music]
a very warm welcome to our foreign
not too bad not too good it's been
trading in a Range however it is forming
what we call as a rounding bottom
formation on monthly charts and it's
trading above the cloud on the monthly
setup that is a positive saying it's
forming what we call as a bullish
ichimoko C Clan
[Music]
and if the levels of three thousand
three thousand fifty SS team you can
head towards develop for 3400 3500 uh
with a span of two months this is also a
time when one should be looking for low
beta stocks as the current test sugar
Market is quite volatile and it might
also see sound of our performance if you
look at Nifty ID that has been more
or less stable compared to other high
beta sectors uh on that first structure
it is also looking to provide some
cushion for any forward we can
experiment Nifty one can keep a stop
loss on a closing basis of around
and play for Tiger price of levels of
3500.
as a disclaimer I do not have any person
holding in the stock but it is possible
that we may have advised this to a class
at input capital thank you
[Music]
foreign